Adam Horne

5 Fox Lane, Winchester, Hampshire, SO22 4DX

Phone: 07807819410 E-Mail: adam@madamot.com Website: www.madamot.com

I create digital products to help businesses be more efficient and provide better experiences to their end-users. I'm a dedicated Digital Media Development student building full stack apps and websites, specialising in React, React Native and Django.

Developer - Love Winchester App - September 2019 to Date

Creating a cross-platform app for the city of WIncherster. The end goal being to engage, inform and inspire residents and tourists alike while being able to promote the city, its history, culture and local businesses. This was achieved by incorporating an interactive map of the city, including points of interest and walking trails around the city with AR aspects and gamification for engagement. (JS, React JS, JSX, Python, Django Rest Framework).

Developer - EJVNails.com - August 2019

Working with a nail technician we wanted to figure out a more efficient way to serve existing and attract new customers. She wanted to stand out and bring something new to the industry so we came up with an online set builder. Potential and existing users can visit the website and build the set they want before booking an appointment. (React JS).

Work Experience - MPC - August 2017

I had the opportunity to contribute to a Nike Air Max 97 advert. In a team of VFX artists I was able to use Illustrator in order to create vector graphic assets to be used in the final video. (Illustrator)

Work Experience - TES - August 2016

During my time there I used Photoshop and Illustrator to create, edit and enhance images and vectors to go along with articles for print and web. I designed various page layouts using InDesign that were printed in TES and TES (Scotland) magazines. (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)

Work Experience - HegartyMaths.com - October 2015 to June 2016

I was appointed as lead designer and was able to use my skills to design business cards using Photoshop, design and develop potential website mock-ups in HTML and CSS and design and develop a website log-in box. My role also included testing of the website to ensure correctness in operation, Analysing problem reports generated by users of the website.

Part-time Job - Asda, Eastleigh - May 2017 to Date

EDUCATION

University of Winchester - September 2018 to Date

Digital Media Development BSc (Hons)

Queensmead School - 2010 to 2017

Maths, Product Design, Business, ICT

ACTIVITY & AWARDS

UoW Business School Award – Outstanding Overall Academic Achievement - 2018/2019 UoW Scholar